Denys Dudnyk

Nitra, Slovakia <u>info.dudnyk@gmail.com</u> +421951232570 <u>My portfolio</u>

Seasoned front-end and back-end developer with strong Javascript skills and 2+ years of experience. I have worked on a varying number of projects, developing personal and commercial products. Currently looking for a full-time job where I can apply and improve my knowledge.

Work Experience

Full Stack Developer

Education In Slovakia - Slovakia edu-slovakia.com/en August 2023 to December 2023

I was developing the frontend and backend parts. There was also implemented a multilingual feature on the website.

Full Stack Developer

SIGMANIT - Estonia March 2023 to August 2023

I developed and maintained a website for the sale of chemical components.

ONLINE CINEMA

htmllessons.io October 2022

I was developing a website using React(Next JS) + NestJS. I created a fully functional online cinema with authorization (with JWT tokens and passport.js) and an admin panel through which it was possible to track statistics of views of a particular film, adding, editing (Draft.js) and deleting films, users, actors, genres related to films. The function of adding a movie to Favorites was also introduced; this function is tied to a specific user. A custom video player for playing movies has also been developed. There is also a rating system that determined the best film depending on its reviews and much more.

Education

Higher Education - Applied Informatics

Constantine the Philosopher University in Nitra -Nitra, Slovakia September 2019 to May 2024

Skills

- React JS (Next JS)
- Axios
- React Query
- Redux
- SCSS
- Git
- React Router Dom
- HTML5
- CSS3

- JavaScript (ES6+)
- Tailwindcss
- Typescript (TS)
- Node.js(Express.js)
- MongoDB
- JWT
- Nest.js

Languages

- English Expert
- Russian Fluent
- Ukrainian Fluent
- Slovak Expert

Certifications and Licenses

htmllessons.io

June 2022 to March 2023

I have studied courses on Web development and learned the technologies I needed for front-end and back-end development.